const Data = [
  {
    question:
      "In context of early vedic period, what does the term 'Gaudhuli' mean ?",
    options: [
      "Measure of time",
      "Measure of distance",
      "search for cows",
      "Guest for whom a cow is slaughtered"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is Sattriya ?",
    options: [
      "Folk Music",
      "Folk Theatre",
      "Classical Music",
      "Classical Dance"
    ],
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Who appoints Chief Justice of India ?",
    options: [
      "Prime Minister",
      "Parliament",
      "President",
      "Seniormost Judge of Supreme Court"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the following first put the demand of constituent Assembly ? ",
    options: [
      "Jawahar Lal Nehru",
      "M.N Roy",
      "Dr. B.R. Ambedkar",
      "Rajendra Prasad"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whom does the Speaker of Lok Sabha submit their resignation to ?",
    options: [
      "President",
      "Prime Minister",
      "Vice-President",
      "Deputy Speaker of Lok Sabha"
    ],
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which among the following terms were not present in the preamble of original constitution of India?",
    options: ["Liberty", "Republic", "Secular", "All of the above"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the following was not a member of the cabinet mission ? ",
    options: [
      "Pethick-Lawrence",
      "A.V Alexander",
      "Sir Stafford Cripps",
      "Lord Wavell"
    ],
    answer: 4
  },

  {
    question: "Who among the following was the founder of Prarthana Samaj ?",
    options: [
      "M.G. Ranade",
      "Aatmaram Pandurang",
      "Swami Dayanand Saraswati",
      "Raja Ram Mohan Roy"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term ‘Goldilocks Zone’ is often seen in the news in the context of",
    options: [
      "the limits of habitable zone above the surface of the Earth",
      "regions inside the Earth-like planets in outer space",
      "search for the Earth-like planets in outer space",
      "search for meteorites containing precious metals"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Who propounded the Doctrine of Lapse Theory ?",
    options: [
      "William Bentick",
      "Richard Colley Wellesley",
      "Lord Dalhousie",
      "Warren Hastings"
    ],
    answer: 3
  }
];
export default Data;
